What are you doing?!
Remember the formations from our training!
Empress!
Clay Platoon, follow me!
Kassim Platoon, get on the other side!
Open formation!
She's wide open!
Take aim!
Now!
Fire!
Keep it up!
It's working just like we did in training!
Now!
I see now.
Initiate long-range attacks once you're
sure Clay Platoon has fallen back!
So they're constantly
targeting her blind spot.
Yep.
A fine strategy that puts their
collective nature to good use.
But there's one problem.
Ordinary attacks won't inflict any
damage on a dragon sheathed in scales.
Well? What now?
Episode 4
The Rosewood Academy Training Exercise
Please bring anyone who's injured this way!
I'll tend to their wounds!
It seems like you're waiting for something.
However, this battle's going
to come to an end before that.
Don't let it hit you!
Okay, now's your chance!
Asmodeus!
That may have done some paltry damage,
but it looks like your plan has failed.
No, it's more than enough.
Now she's lost awareness of her surroundings.
A pitfall?
I thought you were fighting fair and square.
It'd be an unfair trap if it
had been set up beforehand,
but that's not the case.
He dug it out.
After the battle had already begun.
So you were stalling for time all along.
That's not enough to beat her, though.
I know that.
Our real battle begins now.
Go!
Forgive me, Cu.
Asmodeus!
As mighty as I may be...
Huh?
Using me repeatedly like this...
Don't be such a wimp!
Leonard, can you keep fighting?
Yes, my lord!
Leonard!
I've still got stamina to spare.
I haven't failed to run those ten kilometers
you asked of me every morning.
I said what now?
What?!
She's about to take off!
Earnest!
W-Wait!
I refuse!
Sophie!
Artificial Great Hero Power:
Gravity Manipulation.
Now, Earnest!
Sheesh, you're working us to the bone...
I command thee in the
name of Earnest Flaming!
O sword! Demonstrate thy power!
No more... Pwease!
Shut your trap!
Who knew we had such a
capable student at our school?
It's not just her powers.
Even in the advanced class, there aren't
many who can hone their fighting spirit.
But...
Even us students in the lower classes...
Can serve as conduits...
To gather power from everyone!
We also...
Want to be friends with Cu!
Please, Anna!
Grant strength to my lord!
Earnest!
It's in your hands, Empress!
Get her good, Anna!
I leave the rest to you.
Go forth!
Get a good look, Cu.
This is what humans can do.
Cu.
I ended up losing.
You sure did.
I disappointed you, Parent.
Weak children get abandoned, right?
I wouldn't do that.
Besides, you're wrong about one thing.
It's not that you were weak.
Humans were just stronger.
Well? Will you admit it now?
Aye.
Does that mean you can be friends with them?
I-I suppose I must, if you insist.
I don't mind becoming friends with—
Hey!
You know that's not it!
U-Um...
P-Please... be...
Be friends with me!
Of course!
Let's get along, Cu!
So cute!
Hey, be careful!
I see you're in high spirits, Gil.
What are you scheming this time?
I'm happy to see my students grow.
Since they can harness their fighting
spirit and spiritual energy now,
I've arranged a training method
that's even more hands-on.
By which you mean that device?
Indeed.
It's called virtual reality, made using a
once-lost branch of magic called science.
I eagerly await its completion!
Cu, Cu.
Okay, open wide.
I-I can feed myself!
In that case, are you
going to sit by yourself?
Here, open wide!
Just this once.
So cute!
Now, c'mere!
Sit here!
Right here!
You sure are demanding!
So cute! So adorable!
Cuddle, cuddle!
Claire, stop it!
Hey, Earnest...
Is there something different about you?
Huh?
Hey!
Blade!
C'mon, man!
You can't say that, Blade!
You truly are despicable.
Um... You really haven't changed.
No, you have!
You've totally changed!
Pay him no mind, my lord.
Your rotund self is just as lovely!
Don't say it!
Oh, yeah!
It was your weight!
You got fat!
I thought you'd gotten bigger!
I-I get it!
Do you really need to rub it in?!
Blade, you moron!
Guilty.
Eh?
I was in the wrong?
I wouldn't be surprised
if you two were through!
Through?
There, there, Parent.
Blade's really taking it hard.
Well, it's been three days since
Anna locked herself in her room.
Who knew that being "through"
meant I couldn't see her anymore?
That's not it.
Huh?
So what does "through" mean?
It's like, "We can't be friends anymore!
We're through being friends!"
What?!
No! I don't want that at all!
I wanna stay friends with Earnest!
Will she forgive me if I apologize?
I'll go and say sorry to her!
Wait!
Blade, you don't know why
Anna's mad at you, right?
You're only going to make her angrier!
Yep.
That's why we'll tag along as well.
Yeah. I'm worried about how Anna's doing.
And because we're friends, of course.
Yeah!
Thank you!
Are you free?
Blade's here to apologize
for what he said.
Anna, I'm opening the door.
Anna...
Are you crying?
Is everything okay?
Can we come in?
Looks tasty!
Let me have some, too!
You've got so much!
Hey, what?!
You can spare some of it!
Cu, you can see like this?!
Give it to me!
Someone turn on the lights!
D-Don't look!
Please, don't look at me!
These desserts are so tasty!
These desserts...
So that's the culprit.
Ever since our fight against Cu...
I started feeling hungry all the time...
Besides...
I never realized before that all
of this delicious food existed!
Hey, Earnest...
Let me ask you one thing.
Are you and I through as friends?
N-No way!
I didn't... want you to see me like this.
So I couldn't bear to talk with you...
I see!
So we aren't through, then!
What a relief.
Well, I'm leaving.
Hold it right there!
You can't be serious, Blade!
If you leave now, Anna's
gonna end up a lost cause!
Something nice!
You need to say something nice, or else!
Something nice?
Enjoying those desserts?
Good for you.
Blade!
You're twisting the knife!
Huh?!
What should I say, then?
Leonard, show him how it's done!
Yes!
My lord, I remain tirelessly devoted to you.
No matter how overweight you may be.
Who are you calling overweight?!
Earnest.
This isn't something you
can deal with alone, is it?
If not, then turn to us.
All of us will help you out!
What you need is training!
We're friends, aren't we?
Okay! I'll do it!
Hey, stop eating!
Should we go a little slower?
If it doesn't hurt...
I won't be burning calories!
Step, step, step.
19!
You're doing great!
20!
I'm here to cheer you on as your friend!
21!
Step, step, step.
Okay! Keep it up, Earnest!
There! Push harder!
Okay, good!
Step, step, step.
I had the kitchen prepare a
special meal, just for you.
Huh? That's all?
Yes.
You need to cut your calorie intake as well.
I'm so hungry...
The water feels so good!
It's so hot!
How come it hasn't gone down?!
Yikes, that ain't good.
This won't do.
It almost feels like it's gone up.
What's going on?!
THUD
Hey!
How's it look?
Hey! Don't peek!
You're a real hero.
N-No!
Not at all!
I'm definitely not a hero!
I'm just an ordinary guy!
What?
You know, Anna, you should have
put on some muscle from training.
I'm sure you'll slim down in no time.
You think?
Yeah.
If only there were an easier way
to raise your metabolic rate.
I wanted to try something a
little more drastic today.
Something drastic?
Yeah.
This is Testing Ground No. 2, and it's
protected by a powerful magic barrier,
so there shouldn't be any casualties,
even if this goes wrong.
Um...
If I can pull this off and lose weight...
can you praise me for it?
Huh? Sure.
I'm counting on you if
anything happens, Blade.
S-Sure.
I command thee in the
name of Earnest Flaming!
O sword! Consume my flesh!
Use it as thy power!
That's...
This is where you two were!
Wait, what is that thing?!
Is that Earnest?
What? Anna?!
Stay calm. Have faith in her.
Still!
Looks like it worked.
But man, that was scorching hot.
I thought I was gonna die.
Verily.
Thy flesh hath now perished.
Huh? What's that voice?
Asmodeus, probably.
Hold thy head high with pride.
'Tis not since thy first ancestor
that one hath attained this form.
What happened to Earnest's body?
Succumbed flesh doth become
flame by mine hand.
An undying body,
wholly immune to attacks physical!
Come!
Where is thy nemesis, worthy of this form?
Show me thy foe to set ablaze!
My foe to set ablaze...
That would be my body fat!
Pardon?
Because I did this all for my diet!
Diet?
I'm burning so much energy!
It must use up a ton many calories!
I-Indeed.
The drawback to this demon form lies
with the enormous energy it consumes.
Maintaining this form requires
one million calories every hour...
One million!
Who's got time to slowly
jog off those pounds?!
Just burn it all away in a flash!
Yes! Yes!
Hey, are you all right?
I think I'm at my limit...
Grooooowl
I'm so hungry now...
What?!
I'm... hungry!
She's gone into some kind of beast mode?!
She grew a tail.
Anna! Don't abandon your humanity!
Claire...
Thank goodness!
She said my name!
Claire...
Looks tasty!
Dragon Series, Third Sword.
Dragon Banish!
Wind pressure-only version.
Blade, I...
You did great.
Don't look!
Don't look at me!
So you're eating again.
I-It's fine, y'see!
If I turn into a flame demon,
I can lose it again in no time! Y'see?!
Y'see?
That's an excuse for losers.
I said it's fine!
It's fine, okay?!
It's fine!
That's right!
Dieting is the best!
Next Time
The Demon King's Daughter